actfind.com 2008-04-21

# Help and Information From China

**Privacy Notice**

**Collection of information**

When you visit ActFind.com, we do not collect personally identifiable information about you, except when you specifically and knowingly provide it. For instance, we do require registration for the newsletter. If you decide to register for the newsletter, or if you request information from us, you will be asked to provide certain information and details, including your name, country and e-mail address. 

**ActFind.com respects your privacy**

We will not sell, trade or rent personally identifiable information about our users to other parties, without our users' consent. 

We do, however, share certain aggregate information about our users to our suppliers, for example, what percentage of site visitors are from North America. This enables us to better serve you by offering the right product at the right time to the right place. 

We also reserve the right to disclose user information in special cases. For example, when we have reason to believe that such disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be infringing the law (or threatening to infringe) or who may otherwise be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally), our title, rights, interests or property, or those of other web site users, or of anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. We also reserve the right to disclose, without notice to you, personal information in response to a subpoena or other judicial order or when we believe in good faith that such disclosure is required by any law, regulation or listing requirement, or by any stock/securities exchange, governmental or regulatory authority. 

**Use of information**

We may use the information you provide to respond to your requests for additional information, to contact you, if necessary, to service your account or for other administrative purposes. We may also access your information to resolve disputes, to troubleshoot problems, to enforce agreements between us, or for marketing purposes. In addition, for certain transactions, our system may use your transaction details to automate and to streamline your transaction by checking for electronic data compliance, providing reporting features, and transferring data from previous forms to those of the current transaction. 

We may also use the information you provide for certain mailing initiatives. For example, you may sometimes receive an invitation to answer surveys or try out new products and services from ActFind.com. Your feedback helps us develop new products and services based on your needs. 

You always have a choice about receiving mailings, surveys or information about products and services from us. Each e-mail you receive has an "Unsubscribe" option. As a registered member, you can also advise us which types of e-mail you wish to receive by updating "My Account" page. 

**Can I Correct or Remove Information on ActFind.com?**

You always have the option to view your account to make sure the information we have collected from you is indeed correct. You also have the option of removing any information from your account that you wish to keep private. However, please note that removing certain information such as your email address, contact information, and the like may greatly hinder our ability to effectively provide the service or products you have requested. We recommend, that you contact us first to discuss which information you may remove without interrupting the quality of service we intend to provide for you.  Your account will always require a minimum amount of detail to stay open.  Mandatory fields are clearly identified.

 **Changes of Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time. However, if any changes do occur, we will publish the changes on our web site and take reasonable steps to contact you personally to let you know of the new changes. We will also take reasonable steps to contact you personally to let you know of the new changes. Should the company be bought or sold to someone else, we will take reasonable steps to notify you personally. You may choose to continue trading under your account or close your account.

 **If any information you need is not available here, please  [ _Contact Us Now_](http://www.actfind.com/contact_us.php?osCsid=3c0a8817d6625563d4987072861a7cef "ActFind.com Contact us info")!**
